Finding Aid for the Collection of Underground, Alternative and Extremist Literature LSC.0050
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Organization Materials
  - S
    - Socialist Book Shop. Los Angeles, California. (Box 148)
    - Socialist Education Committee. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 148)
    - Socialist Information & Research Bureau. Glasgow, Scotland. (Box 148)
    - Socialist Labor Party. New York, New York. (Box 148, 151)
    - Socialist League. London, England. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Literature Company. New York, New York. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Party - Social Democratic Federation. New York, New York. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Party of Great Britain, n.p. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Party of Los Angeles, n.p. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Party of New Zealand, n.p. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Publication Society. Brooklyn, New York. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Union of Central-Eastern Europe. London, England. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Union Party. Los Angeles, California. (Box 151)
    - Socialist Workers Party, n.p. (Box 152)
    - Socialistic Co-Operative Publishing Association. New York, New York. (Box 152)
    - Society for Cultural Relations USA/USSR. Los Angeles, California. (Box 152)
    - Society for the Prevention of World War 3, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 152)
    - Society for the Psychological Study of Social Issues, n.p. (Box 152)
    - Society of Separationists. Austin, Texas. (Box 152)
    - Soil and Health Society. Emmaus, Pennsylvania. (Box 152)
    - Soledad Brothers Defense Committee. San Francisco, California. (Box 152)
    - Solidarity. London, England. (Box 152)
    - Sons of Liberty. Hollywood, California. (Box 152)
    - Sons of the American Revolution, n.p. (Box 152)
    - Sostre, Martin, 1923-, n.p. (Box 152)
    - Sound Prosperity League. Cincinnati, Ohio. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Alliance Against Racism and Political Repression. Los Angeles, California. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Citizens Against 30-Thursday. Los Angeles, California. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Committee Against Neo-Nazism and Anti-Semitism. Los Angeles, California. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Committee for the People's World, n.p. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Conference to End the War In Vietnam. Los Angeles, California. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Congress of Youth. Los Angeles, California. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Council for a Sane Nuclear Policy. Los Angeles, California. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Federation of Temple Youth, n.p. (Box 152)
    - Southern California Prison Coalition. Los Angeles, California. (Box 153)
    - Southern California Regional American Youth Congress. Los Angeles, California. (Box 153)
    - Southern California School of Anti-Communism. Culver City, California. (Box 153)
    - Southern Californians for New Politics. Venice, California. (Box 153)
    - Southern Christian Leadership Conference. Atlanta, Georgia. (Box 153)
    - Southern Conference Educational Fund, Incorporated, New Orleans, Louisiana. (Box 153)
    - Southern Conference for Human Welfare. Nashville, Tennessee. (Box 153)
      Note: The Southern Patrol (November 1945).
    - Southern Conservative. Lexington, Virginia. (Box 153)
    - Southern Libertarian Messenger, Florence, South Carolina (Box 153)
    - Southern Poverty Law Center, Montgomery, Alabama. (Box 153)
    - Soviet News. London, England. (Box 153, Box 154)
    - Spanish Press Services Limited. London, England. (Box 155)
    - Speakers & Talent Organized for Peace. Los Angeles, California. (Box 155)
    - Special Reports, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 155)
    - Spider. Oakland, California. (Box 155)
    - Spinoza Institute of America, Brooklyn. New York, New York. (Box 155)
    - Spring Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, n.p. (Box 155)
    - Square World Libertarian Front (Squares). Los Angeles, California. (Box 155)
    - Stanford Committee for Peace in Vietnam. Stanford, California. (Box 155)
    - Statesmanship Foundation. Inglewood, California. (Box 155)
    - Statewide Conference Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 155)
    - Sterilization, n.p. (Box 155)
    - Steuben Society of America, n.p. (Box 155)
    - Stop Aid to Marcos. San Francisco, California. (Box 155)
    - Strikes and Lockouts, n.p. (Box 155, Box 156)
    - Student League for Industrial Democracy. New York, New York. (Box 156)
    - Student Mobilization Committee. New York, New York. (Box 156)
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, n.p. (Box 156)
    - Student Peace Union. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 156)
    - Student Statesman Headquarters. Los Angeles, California. (Box 156)
    - Student Struggle for Soviet Jewry, n.p. (Box 156)
    - Student Voice, Incorporated. Atlanta, Georgia. (Box 156)
    - Student West. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 156)
    - Students for a Democratic Society. Los Angeles, California. (Box 156)
    - Students for America. Hollywood, California. (Box 156)
    - Students for Democratic Action. Los Angeles, California. (Box 157)
    - Students to Oppose Participation in the National Student Association (STOP-NSA). Washington, D.C. (Box 157)
    - Studio Blue Print Company. Hollywood, California. (Box 157)
    - Support Our Soldiers (SOS). Sherman Oaks, California. (Box 157)
    - Survey Associates, Incorporated. East Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania. (Box 157)
    - Synanon Foundation, Incorporated, n.p. (Box 157)
  - T
    - TACT Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 157)
    - Tarrytown Group. Tarrytown, New York. (Box 157)
    - Tattler. Hollywood, California. (Box 157)
    - Taxation, n.p. (Box 158)
    - Teachers Against Propostion 14. Los Angeles, California.
      General
      See Civil Rights.
    - Teachers Defense Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 158)
    - Teachers Union, Local 555, U.P.W. New York, New York. (Box 158)
    - Technocracy. New York, New York. (Box 158)
    - Temple Biblical News Analysts. Waco, Texas. (Box 158)
    - Third Force Movement. Bucks, England. (Box 158)
    - Third Foundation. Los Angeles, California. (Box 158)
    - Thomas and Nelson Independent Committee. New York, New York. (Box 158)
    - Thomas Jefferson Club. Los Angeles, California. (Box 158)
    - Tocsin. Berkeley, California. (Box 158)
    - Today's World. Miami, Florida. (Box 158)
    - Toiler. Cleveland, Ohio. (Box 158)
    - Toiler Publishing Association. Cleveland, Ohio. (Box 158)
    - Tom Mooney Labor. San Francisco, California. (Box 158)
    - Tom Mooney Molders Defense Committee. San Francisco, California. (Box 158)
    - Toward Freedom. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 158)
    - Town Hall. Los Angeles, California. (Box 158)
    - Town Hall, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 158)
    - Trade Union - U.S., n.p. (Box 159)
    - Trade Union Educational League. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 159)
    - Trade Unionists for Peace. Los Angeles, California. (Box 159)
    - Trade Unions - Canada, n.p. (Box 159)
    - Trade Unions - Europe, n.p. (Box 159)
    - Trade Unions - Great Britain, n.p. (Box 159)
    - Trade Unions - Sweden, n.p. (Box 159)
    - Trade Unions - U.S., n.p. (Box 160, Box 161, Box 162, Box 163, Box 164, Box 165, Box 166)
    - Traditional Indian Land and Life Committee, n.p. (Box 167)
    - Transcendentalism, n.p. (Box 167)
    - Transport a Child. Los Angeles, California. (Box 167)
    - Trials (espionage) - U.S., n.p. (Box 167)
    - Tribune. A Quarterly Organ of Negro Thought and Opinion. Los Angeles, California. (Box 167)
    - Trumbo, Dalton, n.p. (Box 167)
    - Trustees for Conservation. San Francisco, California. (Box 167)
    - Truth Corps. Hollywood, California. (Box 167)
    - Try Incorporated. Los Angeles, California. (Box 167)
    - Turn Toward Peace. New York, New York. (Box 167)
    - Twentieth Century Fund. New York, New York. (Box 167)
  - U
    - U.S. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities, n.p. (Box 171)
    - U.S. China Friendship Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 170)
    - U.S. Committee Against Nuclear War. Washington, D.C. (Box 170)
    - U.S. Committee for Democracy in Greece. Washington, D.C. (Box 170)
    - U.S. Committee for Justice for Latin American Political Prisoners. Hollywood, California. (Box 170)
    - U.S. Congress. House. Committee on Un-American Activities, n.p. (Box 170)
    - U.S. English. Washington, D.C. (Box 171)
    - U.S. Supreme Court, n.p. (Box 171)
    - UCLA Vietnam Day Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 167)
    - Ultramontanism, n.p. (Box 167)
    - Understanding. El Monte, California. (Box 167)
    - Understanding Unit #15 of Inglewood, n.p. (Box 167)
    - Unemployed Persons Lobby. San Gabriel, California. (Box 167)
    - Unified Family. Los Angeles, California. (Box 167)
    - Union for Democratic Action. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 167)
    - Union for Democratic Action Educational Fund, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 167)
    - Union Label League Bulletin. Denver, Colorado. (Box 167)
    - Union of American Exiles, Toronto, Ontario. (Box 167)
    - Union of Councils for Soviet Jews. Washington, D.C. (Box 167)
    - Union Publishing Association. New York, New York. (Box 167)
    - Unitarian Fellowship for Social Justice, n.p. (Box 168)
    - Unitarian Service Committee, n.p. (Box 168)
    - Unitarian Universalist Service Committee. Boston, Massachusetts. (Box 168)
    - United Action for Animals, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 168)
    - United American Patriots. Los Angeles, California. (Box 168)
    - United American Spanish Aid Committee. New York, New York. (Box 168)
    - United Civil Rights Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 168)
    - United Committee of South Slavic Americans. New York, New York. (Box 168)
    - United Committee to Free Angela Davis. Los Angeles, California. (Box 168)
    - United Cooperative Industries. Los Angeles, California. (Box 168)
    - United Defense Organization. Los Angeles, California. (Box 168)
    - United Farm Workers. Los Angeles, California. (Box 168)
    - United Farm Workers Organizing Committee. Delano, California. (Box 168, Box 169)
    - United Food & Commercial Workers Union. Los Angeles, California. (Box 169)
    - United Freedom Voters Association, n.p. (Box 169)
    - United Jewish Appeal for Refugees and Overseas Needs, n.p. (Box 169)
    - United Labor & People's Committee for May Day. New York, New York. (Box 169)
    - United Mexican-American Students. Los Angeles, California. (Box 169)
    - United Minute Men and Women of America. Los Angeles, California. (Box 169)
    - United Nations, n.p. (Box 169)
    - United Negro Labor Community Council. Los Angeles, California. (Box 170)
    - United Prisoners Union. Sacramento, California. (Box 170)
    - United Progressive News. Los Angeles, California. (Box 170)
    - United Resistance Fund. San Francisco, California. (Box 170)
    - United States Committee for Refugees. New York, New York. (Box 170)
    - United States Servicemen's Fund. Cambridge, Massachusetts. (Box 171)
    - United World Federalists, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 171)
    - United Youth Committee To Aid Spanish Democracy, n.p. (Box 171)
    - Universal Co-operative Union. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 171)
    - Universal Life Church, Incorporated. Modesto, California. (Box 171)
    - University Committee on Vietnam of UCLA, n.p. (Box 171)
    - University Federation for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, New York. (Box 171)
    - Urban West. San Francisco, California. (Box 171)
    - USARE, n.p. (Box 171)
    - Utopian Messenger. Los Angeles, California. (Box 171)
    - Utopian Militant. Los Angeles, California. (Box 171)
    - Utopian Society of America, n.p. (Box 171)
  - V
    - Valley Peace Center. Van Nuys, California. (Box 171)
    - Vanguard, n.p. (Box 171)
    - Venezuelan Civil and Military Movement, Caracas. (Box 171)
    - Venice Draft Information Service. Venice, California. (Box 171)
    - Veritas Foundation. New York, New York. (Box 171)
    - Veterans League of America. New York, New York. (Box 171)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars of the U.S., n.p. (Box 171, Box 172)
    - Vietnam, n.p. (Box 173, Box 174, Box 175)
    - Vietnam Day Committee. Berkeley, California. (Box 172)
    - Vietnam GI. Los Angeles, California. (Box 172)
    - Vietnam Summer. Cambridge, Massachusetts. (Box 172)
    - Vigilant Women for the Bricker Amendment. Los Angeles, California. (Box 172)
    - Vivisection Investigation League. New York, New York. (Box 172)
    - Voice of Americanism. Glendale, California. (Box 172)
    - Voice of Truth & Freedom. Anaheim, California. (Box 172)
    - Voter Education Project, Incorporated. Atlanta, Georgia. (Box 172)
  - W
    - W.E.B. Du Bois Clubs of America, n.p. (Box 175)
    - War - Economic Aspects, n.p. (Box 172)
    - War Registers International, n.p. (Box 172, 175)
    - War Resisters League. New York, New York. (Box 175)
    - Washington Observer Newsletter. Torrance, California. (Box 175)
    - Waste-more-land, General, n.p. (Box 175)
    - Water Moccasin Hoax, n.p. (Box 175)
    - Watts Compton Improvement Association. Los Angeles, California. (Box 175)
    - We, the People. Chicago, Illinois. (Box 175)
    - Weik, Mary H., n.p. (Box 175)
    - West Coast Committee for Democracy in Greece. Berkeley, California. (Box 175)
    - West Coast Socialist Youth Conference, n.p. (Box 175)
    - West End Community Council. Louisville, Kentucky. (Box 175)
    - West Meets East Committee. New York, New York. (Box 175)
    - Western Destiny. Sausalito, California. (Box 175)
    - Western Minute Men U.S.A., n.p. (Box 175)
    - Western Prisoner Information & Support Service. Venice, California. (Box 175)
    - Western Socialist, n.p. (Box 175)
    - Western Voice. Englewood, Colorado. (Box 175)
    - Westside Committee of Concern on Vietnam, n.p. (Box 176)
    - Westwood Village Square. Los Angeles, California. (Box 176)
    - White Sentinel. Ft. Lauderdale, Florida. (Box 176)
    - White Students League. Montrose, California. (Box 176)
    - Whitehorn Defense Fund. Menlo Park, California. (Box 176)
    - William Winter Comments. Sausalito, California. (Box 176)
    - Williams Intelligence Summary. Santa Ana, California. (Box 176)
    - WLA Citizens Committee to Defeat Proposition 24. Los Angeles, California. (Box 175)
    - Women - Employment, n.p. (Box 176)
    - Women - Suffrage, n.p. (Box 176)
    - Women for Legislative Action. Los Angeles, California. (Box 176)
    - Women for Political & Social Action. Altadena, California. (Box 176)
    - Women of America Bipartisan League, n.p. (Box 176)
    - Women of the Pacific. Los Angeles, California. (Box 176)
    - Women Strike for Peace. Los Angeles, California. (Box 176)
    - Women's Christian Temperance Union. Evanston, Illinois. (Box 176)
    - Women's Contingent. Los Angeles, California. (Box 177)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom. Washington, D.C. (Box 177)
    - Women's League of Nations Association. Toronto. (Box 177)
    - Women's Liberation Movement, n.p. (Box 177)
    - Workers Library Publishers. New York, New York. (Box 179)
    - Workers Library Publishers. New York, New York. (Box 180)
    - Workers Library Publishers. New York, New York. (Box 181)
    - Workers Party of America. New York, New York. (Box 181, Box 182)
    - Workers School. New York, New York. (Box 182)
    - Workers Socialist Party of the U.S., n.p. (Box 182)
    - Workers World. New York, New York. (Box 182)
    - Workers' Party of Marxist Unification, n.p. (Box 182)
    - Workers' Socialist Federation. London, England. (Box 182)
    - Workmen's Circle, n.p. (Box 182)
    - World Congress for Leisure Time and Recreation, n.p. (Box 182)
    - World Events Committee. Washington, D.C. (Box 182)
    - World Federation of Trade Unions, n.p. (Box 182)
    - World Federation, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 182)
    - World Hunger, n.p. (Box 182)
    - World Over Press. Wilton, Connecticut. (Box 182)
    - World Peace Council. Helsinki, Finland. (Box 182)
    - World Peace Foundation, n.p. (Box 182)
    - World Tomorrow, Incorporated. New York, New York. (Box 183)
    - World War, -- Propaganda, anti-American -- U.K., n.p., 1939-1945 (Box 183)
    - World War, -- Protest movements, n.p., 1939-1945 (Box 183)
    - World War,, n.p., 1939-1945 (Box 183)
    - World-Truth. Jerusalem, Jordan. (Box 183)
  - Y
    - Yankett Crier. Los Angeles, California. (Box 183)
    - Yanks Are Not Coming Committee. Los Angeles, California. (Box 183)
    - Young Americans for Freedom, Incorporated. Washington, D.C. (Box 183)
    - Young Circle League, n.p. (Box 183)
    - Young Communist International, n.p. (Box 183)
    - Young Communist League, n.p. (Box 183)
    - Young People's Informer. Los Angeles, California. (Box 184)
    - Young Socialist. New York, New York. (Box 184)
    - Youth Publishers. New York, New York. (Box 184)
    - Yugoslavia, n.p. (Box 184)
  - Z
    - Zero Pet Population Growth. Los Angeles, California. (Box 184)
    - Zero Pet Population Growth. Washington, D.C. (Box 184)
    - Zionism, n.p. (Box 184, Box 185)